# REBECCA

# MURRAY

UX/UI Designer

Glasgow, Scotland



+447833394803



rebecca@rebeccamurray.work



rebeccamurraydesign



rebeccamurraydesign

## **Skills**

User Interface Design

Competitive Analysis

User Research and Personas

Iconography and Typography

Branding and Logo Design

Sketching and Wireframing

Copywriting and Mockups

**MVP** Documents

Prototyping and Mockups

#### **Tools**

| Figma      | Sketc | h Invision |
|------------|-------|------------|
| AdobeXD    |       | Indesign   |
| Illustrato | r     | Photoshop  |
| Whimsical  |       | HTML/CSS   |
| Balsamiq   |       | JavaScript |

## Education

**UI Design** February 2022 - October 2022 CareerFoundry (Remote)

**Fashion** September 2012 - June 2016 Heriot-Watt University (Scottish Borders)

Portfolio Prep August 2011 - June 2012 Cardonald College (Glasgow)

# **Personal Profile**

UI/UX designer with a background in fashion design and retail management. Adept at fulfilling client briefs to create confident and clear design work. Experienced at liaising with a variety of team sizes, communicating and collaborating to form solid solutions, creating considered products based on strong data led research.

# **UX/UI Projects**

# HollyHock - Money Saving App

CareerFoundry Case Study

September - October 2022

- Conducted competitive research and analysis of current market.
- Designed a comprehensive brand guideline.
- Established the user journey using user stories, flow diagrams and wireframes.
- Conducted user testing of mid-fidelity wireframes to eliminate pain points early.
- Finalising UI design, including custom illustrations, copy and mockups.
- Created an additional responsive marketing website to highlight features.

# Shoogle - Messaging App

CareerFoundry Case Study

September 2022

- Rapid sketching of wireframes and design with a focus on functionality.
- Creating UI style guides, component guides and typography guides.
- Enriching design with animation and haptic feedback guidelines for developers.

# AccessAtlas - Maps App

June - July 2022

CareerFoundry Case Study

- Conducted competitor research and user interviews to establish goals and MVP.
- Oversaw user testing at low-fidelity stage to establish a clear user experience.
- Researched industry standards to create an accessible icon set and guide.
- Using a mobile first approach, designed a responsive web application with a focus on accessibility, showcasing the implementation of research.

## **Experience**

## Costume Manager - Sweet Charity (Voluntary)

weet Charity (Voluntary) April - October 2022

Green Door Theater

**Junior Designer** 

Wed2b Ltd., Milton Keynes

June - December 2021

- Analysing trends/competitors/company reports to design commercial products.
- Daily use of InDesign and Photoshop to produce technical packs for suppliers.
- Presenting new designs at monthly buying meetings.
- Ollaborating with marketing on new concepts for Website and social content.
- Creating trend/moodboards to be shared within the company and suppliers.
- Collating feedback from our store network to inform future designs
- Working with the wider team to maximise new sustainable ways of working.

#### Store Manager (Mat Cover)

November 2020 - July 2021

Wed2b Ltd., Belfast

 Built and trained a new team. Oversaw daily running and performance of the store, assessing and managing K.P.Is and forecasts and staff performance.

Store Supervisor

July 2019 - November 2020

Wed2b Ltd., Glasgow

Store Supervisor January 2019 - July 2019

Hobbs London, Glasgow

Pattern Maker and Machinist (Seasonal)

P.R.Paterson, Glasgow

January 2018 - March 2018